nepbay.com 2016-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Online Shopping: Shop Online for Mobiles, Electronics, Clothing, Books and More - nepbay.com

NepBay Privacy Policy

How nepbay.com ensures your privacy & what we do with information we collect from you?

Introduction  
Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information.

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub domains of www.nepbay.com.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the User Agreement.

Scope

This privacy policy is applicable only to the domains and sub domains of www.nepbay.com. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users.

Privacy Guarantee 

NepBay promises that we will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. From time to time we may reveal general statistical information about our Web site and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc. Your trust and confidence are our highest priority.

Information

If you choose to buy or sell on the Site (nepbay.com), we collect information about your buying and selling behavior.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

You agree that we may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time.

You agree that we may use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

Access or change your personally identifiable information

To protect your privacy and security, we will verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your personally-identifying information. If you have registered your profile on NepBay, your NepBay ID and Password are required in order to access your profile information.

Security

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies.

Your Consent

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site by NepBay. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Any changes to our privacy policy will be communicated through our Web site.

Account Protection  
Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose your NepBay password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify NepBay and change your password.

Information Disclosure

1\. Advertisements   
a. Where a user enters information on any form of an advertiser, the information is simultaneously collected by NepBay and the advertiser. The information is used by it in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy and is used by the advertiser as per the advertisers prevalent privacy policies. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these advertisers, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to provide the said information.

b. It may also aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes.

2\. City Marketplace Listings   
a. When a user lists an advertisement in City Marketplaces and the advertisement receives an expression of interest by the interested user, the interested user will be provided the contact information of the user listing the advertisement as provided in that user's registration form.

b. When a user expresses an interest in a marketplace listings, the user who has listed the advertisement will be provided the contact information of the interested user as provided in the interested user's registration form.

3\. Items and Services offered on the Site by third parties   
There are certain items and services for which third parties request for information before the item/service is listed on the Site. The information provided by the user for such purposes is simultaneously collected by NepBay and the respective third party. This information is utilized by the third party in accordance with its privacy policy and the terms of the offer. Because we do not control the privacy practices of these third parties, you should evaluate their practices before deciding to use their services.

Other Corporate Entities.   
We share much of our data, including personal information about you, with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries, and joint ventures that are committed to serving your online trading needs and related services, throughout the world. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users.
